LUIS ENRIQUE GUMIEL PARDO

Front end web developer

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Bird

July 19th, 1996

Address

Cota Cota calle 36-A

Phone

+59168030902

Mail

luisegp10@hotmail.com

Portfolio

https://luis-gumielportfolio.netlify.app/

Nationality

boliviana

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/luis-enriquegumiel-pardo-50596b22b

Languages

Spanish

English

Qualities

- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Empathy
- Leadership
- Passion for learn

PROFILE

I'm a passionate person about programming, who seeks to grow every day and expand his knowledge in web development. I have solid knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.JS and MySQL. In backend I have worked with Node.js to build servers, API requests from the frontend and database with MongoDB. I also have experience working with C# and ASP.NET. I have great skills in communication, teamwork, empathy and creativity to personal growth. Right now I seek to improve myself every day and be a better web developer.

EDUCATION

2002-2014 Colegio San Ignacio de Loyola

Bachelor's degree, Humanities

2015-2021 Universidad Privada Boliviana

Engineer's degree, Computer Systems Engineering

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

IT INTERNSHIP

PROESA - Dic 2020- Jul 2020

Management of SQL databases, Technical support in the company and advice on installation and management of programs.

DIRECT WORK

PROESA - Jun 2021- Dic 2021

Implementation of a web application for managing vacations, licenses, medical leave and salary loans. Use of the Laravel framework for project development, Jetstream, AdminLTE, Eloquent, MySQL, Bootstrap, Tailwind and Highchart.js

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

React: zero to expert (Hooks y MERN)

Feb -2023

The course was based on Hooks and functional components, basic JavaScript review, deepening in hooks, states, props, HOC, API requests, MERN, unit tests, hook tests, customHooks, context, Redux, Material UI, Bootstrap Firebase, Moongose, JWT, Google Sign-In,Fetch, mocks, spys, snapshots, ReactReact Testing Library, JEST and production implementations of real projects.

Design Pattern, JavaScript and TypeScript

May -2023

The course includes the following design patterns: Observer, Builder, Singleton .Bridge, Decorator, Strategy and State. Each design pattern included its implementation in JS and in TS. With examples with real cases from day to day and learn to identify when to apply them correctly.

GIT+GitHub: An entire version control system

Jun -2023

The course includes all the basic fundamentals of git, most used commands such as add, commit, checkout, branches, merge, aliases, global configurations, logs, diff, reset, tags, stash, rebase and all remote integration with Github, pull, push, clone, fetch, and pull request. It also includes the management of issues, projects, organizations, teams, pull request merge, tags, releases and gist